(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
On October 3,
the third Last Stage: 24H was revealed.
After the Super Kids Direct Mission,
the four directors who lost are...
up on the Last Stage again.
BADA.
Simeez.
INGYOO.
JEONG MIN JUN.
The four directors are given...
only 24 hours.
The condition given for the Last Stage: 24H.
It is...
umbrellas.
Umbrellas are one of the objects we're most familiar with...
designed to avoid rain.
However, when umbrellas meet lights and videos,
they could turn into a flower field...
or an endless desert...
or a digital space...
or even a new world.
They become objects that create numerous scenes.
(Screaming)
This is driving me crazy.
Actually, I wanted to give up.
(Losing her mind)
This is crazy.
I want to get rid of them all.
I don't care who gets eliminated.
Because I'm going to survive no matter what.
This is made for me.
I can't wait to dance.
I can't wait to show it to people.
It's going to be fun.
It's going to be really intense.
Director BADA...
used umbrellas and the projection depicted a flower blooming...
from a bud.
Director Simeez turned umbrellas...
to an angel's wings, shields, and prison...
and depicted the process...
of a fallen angel.
Director INGYOO turned...
the umbrellas to ninjas' swords...
and used the projection...
to describe the ninjas' mission cheerfully.
Director JEONG MIN JUN completed an intense opening...
by flipping umbrellas and using lights.
He then used umbrellas to describe...
weapons and the Trojan Horse to complete the epic of the Odyssey.
I will announce the first eliminated person...
of the third Last Stage: 24H.
The eliminated person is...
JEONG MIN JUN.
(Eliminated choreographer: JEONG MIN JUN)
Simeez.
(Eliminated choreographer: Simeez)
I really enjoyed watching it, MIN JUN.
You're guaranteed to thrive.
So you can go home with a smile.
Simeez, you're full of potential.
Just as you've been doing,
I look forward to seeing your new world.
Well done.
(You can watch their full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(After the Last Stage)
It smells different.
(Opening the door to his Director's Room for the last time)
So now,
it's time to leave this place.
I can't believe the day has come to put this away.
- When I first joined this show, - Hello.
I wasn't sure about myself.
(What I realized here was...)
(that it's really intense.)
(Who? JEONG MIN JUN?)
(Never heard of his name before)
(He joined his first survival show with passion and confidence.)
(Harsh criticisms on MIN JUN)
Oh, my gosh. He'll be the first one to be eliminated.
- They disregarded me. - That's mean.
I couldn't stop thinking...
about how fragile I was.
Then eventually,
people approved...
of my dance style.
A lot of people liked it.
Well done.
I made friends with nine people.
(Protecting MIN JUN)
Good job, MIN JUN.
Let's go for a meal together next time.
Sounds good to me.
When you joined that team,
did you realize how good I was?
(He never stops showing off.)
I had a really tough time during the K-pop mission.
He basically felt like my savior.
I got to work with capable choreographers,
learn K-pop,
and learn to direct young dancers.
I learned so much.
You're darn crazy.
Just like what the judges said.
You'll be successful.
(Simeez also opens the door to her Director's Room for the last time.)
Oh, gosh.
I didn't know I had these here.
(Simeez spots the knife props from her first mission.)
This reminds me...
of all my efforts
(She never wasted even a moment.)
I was sincere on stage.
I enjoyed every mission.
I got through it in my own way.
(The golden youngest returned in light pink.)
(Her new challenge as a director began.)
(She built a lot of experience as a director...)
(after "Street Woman Fighter.")
(She grew up to be a golden director who leads the stage.)
It feels like I'm trying something new every day.
Everything feels new.
I was completely immersed.
Do you know what it feels like to take the lead every time?
I'm held accountable...
- for everything I say. - You shouldn't go this way.
(The weight of director who has to hold accountable for everything)
It was heavier than I expected.
When I watched your performance today,
I was reminded once again of how amazing you are.
Your challenge.
Your drive.
And your energy.
It's not something anyone can catch up with.
I hope your talent...
continues to shine through in different areas.
And I'll always be rooting for you.
I want to be a director...
who is as unique as I am.
"That's what she wants to do."
"That's what she's good at."
If anyone recognizes that even a little,
I wouldn't regret my decision to join this show.
You look tired.
- You look tired. - No.
- Hee Jung. - Yes.
Well done.
(Well done.)
(Leaving her last message)
The end.
(I finished everything as who I am. Good job, Simeez!)
It's my quality as a golden director.
I've become one.
(I've become a golden director.)
From the start to the end,
I did my best as a director.
I have no lingering feelings and no regrets.
My stories have...
only started.
Please look forward...
to who I am as a person.
It was a good game.
Good game.
Thank you...
for watching my growth.
Bye.
(JEONG MIN JUN)
(The warmth may be gone,)
(but the passion lasts forever.)
The most intense stage before the final,
the semifinal.
Here is your mission.
It's the one I've wanted to do the most.
(Complete...)
(5 different solo performances...)
(in the brand film.)
The benefit is too great.
I want it.
I'll go first.
My concept is...
the spirit.
Yes!
(Yes?)
You'll have to fix your concept a lot.
But is it really worth changing it?
I was quite disappointed in myself.
It wasn't what I expected at all.
It looks like I made a mistake.
Koo Young is too greedy.
I want to work with this director.
You can't find a director like me.
Who's it going to be?
I don't care as long as I'm safe.
- We can only pick one. - Right.
Where are they going?
Are they heading to Koo Young's room?
They're heading to Koo Young's room.
Oh, my gosh.
What? Are they coming to me?
They only chose Koo Young?
(Director Back Koo Young receives a mysterious letter.)
The result of the only one who enters the final.
(Is this the ticket straight to the final?)
(What does it say in the letter?)
(The Brand Performance Film Mission begins now.)
Okay.
I'll see you in the final.
The most intense stage before the final,
the semifinal.
The directing competition that began with ten directors...
has gone through numerous choices and competitions.
Back Koo Young, BABYZOO,
Kasper, BADA, INGYOO.
Only five of them remain.
The semifinal mission is...
What kind of mission is it?
To express the global smartphone brand...
that is loved around the world.
It's the Brand Performance Film Mission.
Oh, my gosh.
Do we get to film it?
A brand performance?
I keep hearing something new every time.
This film...
doesn't just end as a mission.
What does that mean?
Part of your performance film...
will be used in the global smartphone brand's commercial.
(Incredible chance)
Amazing.
While you participate...
in the performance you direct,
you also...
perform as the global smartphone brand's model.
(Performing as the global smartphone brand's model)
That's huge.
That's awesome.
It's something everyone wants to try at least once.
That's crazy. I've always wanted to try...
a smartphone commercial.
Is it my dream come true?
However, this opportunity is...
- given to only 1 director. - Only 1?
A global smartphone brand's commercial model?
I'm dying to do it.
I've never wanted anything so badly before.
I have to get this.
This has to be mine.
I have nothing left to regret.
I really have no regrets except for one thing.
A global model? That sounds cool.
I really want it.
But I never showed that I want it.
I tend to be the quiet one that fools everyone.
It's a chance to become a model...
for the smartphone the whole world goes crazy about...
and become the lead in that film.
That's the biggest perk.
I want it so bad.
I want to be its director so bad.
I will explain how the final director is selected.
Five choreographers will produce their own solo performance films.
It'll be the highlight of the film...
as well as the most important part of the commercial.
All five will be given the same concept,
planning, and production conditions.
Only the one with the most perfect film...
will become the final director of this mission.
Not only the winner will receive the ticket to enter the final,
but also the power...
to save one of the choreographers...
from the Last Stage: 24H.
The winner gets to save one person from the Last Stage.
It'll allow the winner to reach out.
It gives the power to save one.
Winning the power is my priority.
But even if I lose it,
I'd better do my best to be saved.
The section you must complete with your solo performance is...
be explained by the production team director...
who is joining this mission.
Let's bring in the director.
(Cheering and welcoming)
Hi.
(Video Director Kim Hyeong Seok)
(The director of a famous movie distributor's opening sequence...)
(and "World of Street Woman Fighter's" semifinal mission)
(Video Director Kim Hyeong Seok with 15 years of experience)
The title of this brand performance film is...
One Moves Us All.
It was motivated by Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
What you're showing on this show...
isn't just choreography,
but your directing abilities...
to move everything on the stage.
The expansion of that area is...
the concept of this film.
I'm going to direct the narrative section...
of this film.
And I'm going to leave everything...
to you.
He's going to direct the film in general,
and we're director the movement.
I'll get to let my imagination run wild.
Since you're directing the highlight,
the group choreography will take up a big part,
and there will be your solo performance in between.
I hope it's just as impactful as the group choreography.
He said he wants it to be impactful and cool...
even in a single shot.
I'm confident.
My moves are not limpy.
I can make the best of it.
Who will be the one...
to lead the whole brand performance film?
Everyone thinks I'm not impressive enough.
But I have quite a long film experience.
I'm pretty confident.
I can pull this off.
I want to show that I have...
what the other four people don't have in this film.
There's something only I can do.
We will now begin...
the Brand Performance Film Mission.
Ready? Fight.
It'll make me the movement director.
That's why I want it even more.
Showing the most of me...
in a narrow space is...
the mission.
(Expressing a narrow space in the draft)
I just need to do my best.
This solo section must be the killing part.
I believe I have good expression...
when it comes to filming.
Honestly, I couldn't be more confident.
It has to be me.
I tried using a funny filming technique.
Can you do reverse?
(Throwing his jacket)
So when I do that,
my jacket will fly back to me.
I appear rolling.
Then my shadow clones appear.
Then I become one again.
I'm trying to use that kind of filming technique.
I've only started enjoying the air up there.
I want to keep it going.
I'll be the winner in the end.
My choreography has the hand gesture.
If I tape my fingers,
it'll draw attention.
Since I've been on many commercials,
I have a good understanding of commercial music.
I'll bring all my abilities together.
This is what I want to do the most.
Becoming the movement director.
I was so jealous of Koo Young.
I kept trying to break out of the space...
on the floor.
I tried to look explosive.
I was looking for supernova.
- Five, six, seven, eight. One, two. - I'd be better...
in terms of technique movements.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - I'll prove...
why the one that lasts long is strong.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I have to do it.
It'll prove the reason for my existence.
I will take...
the movement director title.
I treated it like pure art.
I discovered the raw material within me,
along with its roots and its rhythm.
My concept is the spirit. Yes!
(Yes!)
Yes!
Hey! Spirit!
The bounce you can't find in any other culture.
I focused on being iconic.
I can create the best result.
Hello.
No way. The judge chairs of fear.
I'm scared.
Gosh. The Solo Film Presentation.
(5 directors created the solo film drafts.)
(5 directors will...)
(present their drafts in order...)
(and explain their concept.)
(How will you express the kick?)
(They're free to ask questions.)
(Groaning)
Gosh. It's going to be so brutal today.
The die is cast.
What's going to happen now?
(Startled)
(The siren sounds more frightening than usual.)
That sound is going to give me a nightmare.
Gosh. The time has come.
Shoot.
No.
(The directors head to the square to present their concept.)
How was it?
- Well... - How was it?
I did my best.
(Crying)
(All 5 directors are seated.)
The presentation is the most nervous part.
- Yes. - Even more nervous than dancing.
I wonder who's going to be here as a judge.
Me too.
Director Kim Hyeong Seok will be one.
They're here.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello.)
(On eggshells)
They're pretty close.
Having them so close made me nervous.
(Judge Shim Jae Won)
Oh, my gosh.
(Judge Kim Hyeong Seok)
Nice to meet you.
(It looks sophisticated even now.)
(How did he think of filming vertically back then?)
(Including his signature work of a vertical music video,)
(he uses various techniques.)
(Art Director Seong Won Mo)
Hello.
You're participating as directors instead of dancers.
I'm going to focus...
on how to direct the performance...
in this film.
I'll evaluate based on that. Thank you.
(Thank you in advance.)
I know you all worked very hard.
I'll watch with respect and gratitude.
Then we will now begin...
the solo performance film presentation.
(Here we go.)
It feels different from doing it just between us.
It finally feels real.
Who wants to show...
his work first?
(Out of nowhere)
(Avoiding eye contact)
(On eggshells)
(Turning)
(Reading the room)
I'll go first.
(Whatever!)
Oh, good job.
(Let's go!)
I like that energy.
My title is...
the same as the synopsis.
Since it's a commercial,
I thought I should spread it to as many people as possible.
My concept is the spirit.
Korea's spirit. Yes!
I interpreted it in my own way.
As if I caught a perch...
somewhere in the sea.
I focused on the message, "One Moves Us All..."
and thought about my one move...
after stripping everything away?
I decided to find my root first.
I focused on excitement...
which is the shared quality between many Koreans including myself.
The rhythm that everyone has...
from an old man to a baby.
Yes!
The old men's dance after getting drunk.
That has the power...
that is not found in any other culture.
I adopted the rhythm in us.
I focused on the striking image...
and the choreography.
Why don't we watch it first?
INGYOO made many unique moves.
I expect INGYOO to come up with something good.
There's got to be an unconventional moment.
Let's go.
(One Moves Us All)
(I take the one rhythm that remains in my body as a seed...)
(and let it germinate through the movements of countless people.)
(Look at that.)
The peace in me scatters.
Then I focused on myself again.
INGYOO has his own unique style.
He put a lot of that in.
The movement can be grasped at a glance.
It's intuitive.
I tried to express what's unique to me,
what only I can create,
without relying on elaborate staging.
(Mega section)
It's INGYOO.
It was interesting.
INGYOO is saying, "You go your own way,"
"and I'll go mine."
The way to approach...
spirit was fascinating.
I sought to express the natural sense...
of joyful energy through my own body.
Apple, let's go.
(Fruit shop, let's go!)
(There's just no stopping INGYOO.)
He defies expectations.
It's very fresh.
It's what I respect about him.
It's really cool...
how he unabashedly expresses his own individuality.
The downside is...
A dove...
searching for the spirit.
(Laughing)
(Failed to hold back laughter)
After seeing the dove come out...
(Gosh)
It's not for me.
The work we do is commercial,
after all.
The movements feel really catchy.
Was that intentional?
Actually, what I was trying to focus on was...
"It's funny..."
was the intention.
It's a commercial.
People's eyes must not leave the film.
The focus was more on...
drawing people in to get them to look.
Once you see this rhythm,
you'll want to do it.
AI can handle everything...
that's flashy and impressive.
The real raw material.
The real raw material I have and its roots.
You're talking about raw materials in the age of AI.
How did you make the doves?
The doves...
There's a hidden meaning here as well.
With what? With AI?
- I made them with AI. - Okay.
Okay. That's all.
(Laughing)
He drives me crazy.
They fly away.
They're disappearing from within my body.
That's it.
INGYOO's attempts always...
boil down to 1 of 2 things.
Either you like it or you don't.
This time...
it's a mismatch.
In any case,
"Is the movement suitable for the commercial?"
"Is the format suitable for a mega crew?"
I thought about that.
I considered a mega crew.
I considered commercial.
It's a move designed for a mega crew.
It has more impact when performed by a mega crew.
It burns into your brain.
It's not just boringly simple.
I thought I was on a different level.
I'm on a different level.
He's funny.
Hello, I'm Kasper.
I titled the work...
"Re Leap."
I incorporated my own story.
There...
(Throat clearing)
At first...
I...
(Throat clearing)
That part...
I'm really nervous.
(Laughing)
(Clearing his throat)
He's nervous, so he buttoned it up wrong.
I think we need to tell him.
I was really nervous.
I didn't know what I was saying.
Rather than not going to the Last Stage,
I really want to do this.
This show...
makes a person feel desperate...
and deeply earnest.
Anyway,
I started dancing when I was young out of curiosity.
I believe that who I am today...
is the result of all those experiences.
I wanted to capture the story...
of my comeback and resurgence.
I started from rock bottom.
I worked really hard.
I spent far too long...
always dancing in the background.
It might feel like a waste of time.
Looking back now,
the lonely path I had been traveling...
all this time has become...
a solid foundation for me.
(Kim Tae-woo, a 23-year-old urban dancer who took on...)
(the challenge of pursuing his dream)
Kasper is a really famous director.
(He was on "Be Mbitious.")
(This moment, made possible by repeated challenges...)
(and a steady, relentless journey)
I wanted to capture...
my own personal history.
(Re Leap)
(Movement Director Kasper)
(Synopsis: After countless efforts, I've finally become a director.)
(Space Utilization Strategy: Limited space. Extended space)
(Good start)
There is a rewinding sound.
I tried to weave in my younger self...
to show why I ended up doing this.
I started dancing with b-boying.
I've got some serious footwork skills, just like MIN JUN.
I thought he would breakdance.
Because it is fast-paced music that lends itself well to b-boying.
A sense of speed and dynamism will be emphasized.
I leaned into the musicality...
and scaled things back a bit for the mega-crew section.
Five Kaspers...
perform...
the Shadow Clone Technique.
The path I have traveled so far...
serves as a solid foundation,
allowing me to showcase my diverse range of capabilities.
(Mega section)
There are no impactful moments in the choreography.
It wasn't clearly conveyed...
how it would be expressed...
when performing with the mega crew.
(Impressed)
Kasper definitely looks cool when he's on stage.
May I drink some water?
I'm so thirsty.
(Laughing)
I'm nervous.
It feels very awkward...
to be the subject.
That's a challenge.
Because I'm not...
as expressive as other people.
It definitely feels awkward.
I'm super nervous.
You're doing well.
(Grateful)
What surprised me while listening was...
that what you said aligned almost perfectly...
with the initial direction I had planned.
You have a good understanding of the storyboard.
You utilized a wall...
in the opening section.
There won't be a wall...
when actually filming.
Yes. Actually, so...
I'm going to do it like a mime.
There won't be a wall,
- so how will you do it? - Yes.
I can make it seem as if there is a wall.
Like a mime.
(Kasper has already prepared a contingency plan.)
It's set up so that it can be done in mid-air as well.
If I were to direct a film...
with Kasper,
it would be great...
to intercut that part.
I think it'd be cool.
I feel like...
I came the closest...
to the direction...
the director envisioned.
I'm curious about...
how you expressed...
the iconic nature of this brand,
which defines the era.
You can just do...
something flashy like that.
But the core...
isn't incredibly heavy like mine.
It's great that there are various ideas and themes,
but they feel like things I've seen before.
In particular, the composited scene...
is one that many people have seen already.
Does it align...
with the brand's established standards?
That brand has its own standards.
Would they want to adopt a visual style...
derived from a reference?
(Thinking)
Iconic...
I was a bit concerned...
that the filming techniques I used...
might not come across as fresh.
It'll probably depend on how they look at it.
Lastly,
there's something I want to say.
I...
(What is it?)
There are many running scenes.
I participated in track and field from the third grade...
through the ninth grade.
(Laughing)
I was a sprinter.
I can run incredibly well.
(I got it.)
That's all.
Wouldn't running be important too?
I'm really good at running.
I'm a sprinter.
Hello, I'm Director BADA.
"Move the Frame."
"Becoming an Icon Through Movement."
This is what I portrayed.
I have come this far...
through movement alone.
The most iconic thing I can create is...
myself.
I myself...
am an iconic person and dancer.
That is my greatest strength.
I aimed to convey my energy to the camera...
and command the screen,
while also capturing plenty of my iconic moves...
and powerful energy.
She projects a powerful presence.
She likely strove to capture it in a multi-dimensional way.
I'm really curious.
Let's check out the video.
("Move the Frame")
(Movement Director BADA)
(Synopsis: Charismatic BADA leads the mega crew)
(Space Utilization Strategy: Expressing the dance's energy)
I feel that the flow best captures the essence of a small space,
so I start with the flow.
The model is attractive.
I admit that the subject is attractive.
It feels like it falls within the expected range.
I wanted to create a movement that felt like drifting in the sky.
I was inspired by the act of knocking on a door.
Riding the wave,
we move from here to the mega crew.
(Immersed)
The wave is...
impactful.
BADA's movements are...
certainly iconic and unique.
It would be great to depict...
each and every finger of the members.
(Mega section)
We'll spin and dance together.
There will be various angles.
(Mega section)
It didn't seem like a challenge.
It seemed like she went for the safe choice.
It was like I was disappearing from this place.
I went with the meaning of traveling to another world.
(That was great.)
(Cheering)
(Clapping automatically)
I definitely felt this from the video.
The iconic image of yours...
was delivered well.
What was a bit disappointing...
was that the video felt a bit hectic.
I thought that it needed to be sorted out.
"What is she planning to do for the mega section?"
(After a body roll,)
(the mega section happens without a transition.)
It was hard to tell where the mega section started.
It didn't move my heart, and it worried me.
If I get the role,
I can send you the fixed version tomorrow.
I'll make sure to get it sent tomorrow.
I felt flustered.
That's how many ideas I have inside my head.
I think it was hard to express it through the video.
I think the Judges wanted...
to see the visual effects...
and performances you wanted to express through the video.
They wanted an overall plan of those things,
but there wasn't a clear idea.
I believe a director should be capable...
of doing more than just coming up with the choreography.
I believe choreography creation...
is one of the abilities a director should have.
I agree with what the Judges said.
There wasn't a specific method...
for the change in angles.
If there were a specific direction...
or transition,
it would've been easier for all of us to understand it.
It was hard to tell when the mega crew was to appear...
and which part was the mega choreography.
None of that was shown in the video.
I should've done more.
I should've expressed myself with more confidence.
I was very disappointed.
Jun Hui and I are left, right?
I want to go home.
(The father who wants to go home)
BABYZOO should go next.
I'll go!
It'll feel the same whenever I go.
- Go! - Go!
- Good luck! - Let's not feel intimidated.
I must look smart.
(He completes the smart BABYZOO look.)
BABYZOO has a similar image to mine.
I'm worried that we would feel similar.
First of all, I would like to thank all of you.
(He starts his presentation with a smart comment.)
I thought about how I could...
deliver my iconic movements...
with a short amount of time.
I went to the practice room...
and tried special moves, new moves,
and moves I haven't done before.
But putting together a part with those moves...
didn't feel right.
That was when I realized this.
"I must be myself to make it feel iconic."
The title of my work is "Becoming."
Where I am right now...
and the process before reaching this far.
I tried to express the emotions...
of the past and present.
I was certain about the emotions.
The screen has to display...
my own feelings...
to be expressed as BABYZOO's iconic energy.
I did a lot of research.
Being true to myself...
was the biggest distinguishing factor.
I think that will be expressed through the video.
We will watch it together.
(Movement Director BABYZOO)
(Synopsis: I'm finally where I wanted to be.)
(Space Utilization Strategy: Unique Energy. Iconic Image)
(Impressed)
Gosh, it was awesome.
Jun Hui filmed a commercial.
Gosh, this feels like a commercial.
"I've made it to this place."
I tried to express that only with my eyes.
Jun Hui has many facial expressions.
I believe that's his strength.
(Mega section)
The nervous and overwhelming emotions...
were expressed through dancing.
I believe it was the best song for BABYZOO to express himself.
(Mega section)
While spinning, I move back to the times I've been through.
Think of me reminiscing about the past.
I did my best to express the intense emotions I felt...
while trying to make it to where I am now.
Every move felt strong.
There were some odd moves that could be seen.
That's great.
Me going through memories of the past. Me in the present.
I expressed the emotions...
of believing that I can move forward again.
I put together a group move.
It seems like I crashed into a wall,
but I get back up from the ground.
(Mega section)
(Clapping...)
(automatically)
That was amazing.
Only Jun Hui can pull that off.
Especially, at the start,
there was a move like this.
"It's quite childish."
Jun Hui came up with wow factor with the directing.
But the dancing was quite disappointing.
I was impressed by the clear presentation.
I got a strong impression that this was a brand film.
I was impressed by that. And regardless of this video,
it made me think, "I want to work with this director."
This presentation and video...
made me want to take this project.
I was greatly impressed by...
your directing abilities.
I'm aware that the director in charge of this...
is really busy.
He's really busy,
but it felt like you came up with the actual product...
that could be used right away.
I thought that it was directed in detail...
and that the director in charge would find it easy to work with.
It starts with the whole group at the start.
You looked into the camera...
before the group joins in. That part felt different...
and I thought it was a good idea.
As he just mentioned,
it seems like I won't have to do much with this.
You've done a great job in a short period of time.
I could've made it stronger and more impactful,
but I believed that a sense of control and empty space...
suited the brand more.
That was why I made a bold choice to empty out some parts.
I have no regrets about what I came up with.
I believe I'm someone...
who has a great sense of expression in films.
I'm really confident and I'm able to say this.
You must pick me.
Hello, I'm Choreographer Back Koo Young.
(Back Koo Young is the last one to go.)
Koo Young has a great understanding of videos.
He's always a concern.
I'm excited to see how impressive his work is.
After he heard about the mission,
his ambition poured out from his eyes.
The mission was about taking the spotlight.
I really wanted to take this role.
"SUPERNOVA" is my concept.
"One spark, infinite energy."
My inspiration...
came from "Explosion of a Star."
A star explodes...
and the stars around explode due to that energy.
I did my best to express that idea.
A small burst of energy expands into a great burst of energy.
(Impressed)
He even brought an image made by AI.
"He secured the Title Sequence Film."
"He's planning to secure this one as well."
"He's up for this." These were the thoughts I got.
I prepared everything with great care.
The highlight in the film...
is the 360° section.
From here to here.
I set the angles based on the movements.
(A 360° turn)
(The camera turns as well.)
I did this dozens of times...
until I got the right cut.
There we go.
While changing conception of the wall and floor,
I wanted to defy gravity...
and express an image...
of penetrating through a limited area.
Once that energy exceeds the limit of that area,
one spark becomes infinite energy.
In the video, the solo dancer would turn into the mega crew.
Koo Young did well with the presentation.
I'm curious about what he came up with.
I was confident in the result that came out.
I will make sure to take the title as Movement Director.
(Movement Director Back Koo Young)
(Synopsis: One ray of light reaches an unfamiliar place.)
(Space Utilization Strategy: Trapped energy exceeds limit)
(Brand Performance Film Mission, Choreography Concept Credit Board)
(Back Koo Young)
(Impressed)
(Solo section)
It started strong.
I wanted to add life to the film...
using angles and transitions.
It was really impressive.
As the angles were unique,
it felt iconic.
As it was a limited space,
I wanted to express a distorted and crumpling image.
(Solo section)
I wish the viewers to find it entertaining.
It was really charming.
He didn't make a name for himself for no reason.
(Solo section)
It didn't feel like he was defying gravity.
I used the jump for an expansion of the area...
to start the mega performance.
As the camera turns, I head back to the solo section.
I didn't understand why it went back to the solo section.
I do another jump to connect to the mega performance.
(Mega section)
The tension and energy were amazing.
(Impressed on mute)
It was a lot more impressive than I expected it to be.
The structure and flow of the performance were impressive.
Koo Young showed that he could be impactful as a player as well.
Compared to the concept,
the dancing and expressions felt too aggressive.
It started with strong energy and ended with strong energy.
I think my body will break from that.
I won't be able to do that.
It would be great if the Judges...
would find this to be the right film for the final chapter.
Your directing abilities...
and dancing abilities stood out in this video.
I was very impressed.
This is what I'm curious about.
The concept is "SUPERNOVA: One spark, infinite energy."
When will that transition of an explosion to infinite energy...
actually happen?
The lights change during the jump.
This was the image I had in my head.
As I jump, the mega crew jumps.
I thought it could be expressed through post-production.
So the director...
will come up with the scene for the explosion?
(Will it not be possible?)
I thought that it was different.
It was completely different from what I expected.
(Flustered)
He must not like it.
But it had a strong impact.
I thought that the way you expressed gravity...
would be really impactful in the master film.
But this is what I'm worried about.
The members of the mega crew have to dance as one.
I have a slight worry about whether that could be expressed perfectly.
If it doesn't work out on site,
everyone will look glum.
He was worried about making the mega crew performance.
It's not a matter of whether it's possible or not.
It's something that must happen.
You won't have to worry about that.
I will do my best to come up with a good performance.
It's all or nothing.
He said it was different from what he expected.
It could be positive or negative.
I hoped to get the role.
I thought that I was the one who came up with...
the best video with energy.
I'm desperate for this.
I'm the most desperate for this one out of all missions.
Please pick me.
That concludes the check of the solo performance films...
of all five choreographers.
To decide on just one director who will become...
the movement director of the Brand Performance Film,
we will have our final discussion.
Please head to your Directors' Room...
and wait for the final result.
(Scared)
Let's leave it to my fate.
- Let's leave it to my fate. - Thank you!
- Thank you! - Thank you!
(Smiling)
You did a great job.
I did my best.
I have no regrets.
They're deciding there?
Gosh, this is crazy.
Can't they do it in a separate room?
Through all of the synopses...
and presentations,
I believe mine stood out...
out of all of them.
If I become the movement director,
I get the right to save one person.
I'm desperate.
Gosh, I'm so curious.
I'm so curious about what's going on at this moment.
It's a bummer that I can't hear anything.
I think mine will feel more impactful...
when they watch it over.
Please go with my idea.
If my idea meets with the director's idea,
I believe a great video will come to life.
I really want to do this.
Everyone would feel that way.
Everyone wants this role.
I hope mine gets picked.
The directors are in a heated discussion.
Do you have the ranks in your head?
I do, but they all have...
- different strengths. - Right.
We are in need of two things.
We need a model...
and directing abilities.
This is the hardest part for me.
I asked them to express an iconic performance.
When you come up with the solo performance,
you might have to consider a group dance as well.
It would be great to have ideas on the transition to the solo part...
and how to make an impact with your appearance.
They all interpreted it differently.
As for INGYOO,
he expressed the spirit of the time and Korean spirit.
- That felt very iconic. - Right.
It gave off Korean vibes.
It made me think, "He came up with this?"
But I was slightly confused...
about the way he expressed himself.
It was great to see him make a new attempt.
It made me want to see his version of this scene,
but I wasn't able to picture it in my head...
after watching the draft video.
INGYOO always makes a different approach.
That's what makes him great,
but I believe it could also go against him greatly.
When I watched this,
I thought it would place 1st or 5th.
- Right. I felt the same. - Right.
If that draft is to be used,
you would have to change...
- quite a lot. - Right.
The wide cut wasn't that great for the mega crew.
- The moves were too simple. - Right.
I thought that there wasn't much to see.
- That was what was disappointing. - Right.
As for Kasper,
it did feel like he just did his own dance.
There wasn't an expansion of space...
and it wasn't a part that utilized space.
Considering the overall impact...
with the group dance and solo dance,
it felt quite weak.
Those who know him...
might understand the story and movement.
But I also believe that those who don't know him...
might struggle to understand his intentions.
Right. I agree with that.
As for Back Koo Young,
I was surprised by him...
- just by his dancing. - Right.
"One can dance like that?"
The level of his dancing was amazing.
His energy as a solo character felt great.
He had his own ideas of the camera movement as well.
Koo Young's part felt too strong.
I wasn't able to understand the flow.
There wasn't a certain connection...
with the synopsis.
His energy as a solo character was great.
His concept was really impactful.
But in my opinion,
it felt one-dimensional.
He went with that concept of energy.
He became the very source of energy...
and set himself as the center of the supernova.
Instead of utilizing the space,
it felt like he expressed his existence within that space.
I felt it was different from what I expected.
As for BADA,
she's unrivaled with her iconic performances...
and her energy from dancing.
The aura she possesses feels so strong.
But this is her blank point.
The mega crew.
- Right. That was missing. - The mega crew...
wasn't expressed in the video.
I should've done a better job.
I had so many things I wanted to express as a mega crew.
I should've put that in the draft.
As it wasn't expressed in the draft,
my words didn't sound convincing.
Why am I like this?
BADA's draft was impressive.
It felt like, "I am BADA."
She put in a lot of her iconic features.
But I wasn't sure if that could bring out a great response.
But the model is charming.
I admit that the figure is charming.
She's captivating and charming...
with her eyes and such.
I gave her a perfect score for this part.
To be honest, her figure was outstandingly charming...
compared to the others.
I also thought...
- she stood out. - She stood out.
Also, she prepared...
- many iconic moves. - Right.
I thought she had great ideas...
and was impressed by that.
(Moves that expressed iconic gestures)
This felt iconic to me.
She filmed the video herself...
and put the camera on the floor before striking a pose.
The scene of her disappearing into the darkness...
felt very creative.
I thought she did well to utilize the space.
Those ending scenes can never be...
- thought of by directors. - Right.
- I can never imagine that. - Right.
- It might not turn out nicely. - Right.
But the problem is that the next video surprised me.
- It was... - Another strong contestant.
BABYZOO was meticulous with his work...
and produced something of great quality.
Right.
I thought that the level of completion...
- was flawless. - Right.
This was what I personally felt.
"Could he be less impactful when he's alone?"
This was the thought I got.
He might have less of an impact...
when he's performing on his own.
Jun Hui came up with wow factor with the directing.
But the dancing was quite disappointing.
As for the model,
the style of dancing has a great influence.
The appearance is important as well.
Gosh, this is killing me.
Before we could even think about it,
BABYZOO divided up the parts in advance.
"He tried to express this in this part."
"This is the angle he wants."
He divided up the parts...
- and I was very impressed by that. - Right.
- It was very clear. - Right.
- I really liked his storyboard. - Right.
I thought that there were a lot of emotions expressed...
along with a touching point in the end.
- The start felt great. - It was great.
He stood alone while the others danced around him.
- It was really impactful. - It was really impactful.
I think it will be great to end with the other dancers.
Based on directing,
I thought that a lot of people would choose this one...
without knowing any of these names.
Right.
It had the biggest impact...
- It was touching. - based on the story.
The overall balance was great...
with his dancing, angles, and directing.
BABYZOO has prepared delicious ingredients to work with.
What's the most important factor?
Based on the concept of a dance film,
who are the ones who can make it eye-catching...
without going beyond the boundaries?
Based on that thought,
I think I would lean toward BADA and BABYZOO.
- They're my top two as well. - Right.
I'm thinking the same way.
Who will it be?
BABYZOO.
(Answering his own question)
I hope I get picked.
I will avoid the Last Stage and head to the final.
I don't want to go to the Last Stage. It can't happen.
Never.
"I'm done if it doesn't work out for me this time."
"It's game over for me if I fail this time."
I kept believing that I was going to get picked.
Iconic.
I'm a true icon.
But it's based on the draft.
Dance like INGYOO when you have a lot in mind.
I've always wanted to put together a smartphone commercial.
It was a personal dream.
I want it so much.
I really want to be picked as the movement director.
(Who will become the movement director?)
BADA is so iconic.
She must've been really compelling as the subject.
BABYZOO was the most prepared.
And his direction had a real hook.
(Who will become Movement Director?)
(Final Movement Director: BABYZOO)
(Really? Me?)
What?
Then the screen turned orange.
(It's really me!)
I totally froze...
Was it really me? That's crazy.
Yes!
I was so happy.
(Good job, me!)
I finally did something on Street World Fighter.
I didn't want to seem overrated again,
so I knew I had to prepare even harder and nail the shoot.
That's what hit me right away.
What?
Congrats.
I was really disappointed.
It was something I'd really looked forward to,
but in that draft video,
I don't think I explained it well enough.
Yes, I was pretty disappointed.
BABYZOO checked all six boxes in this mission.
He said I only checked five.
(During BADA's presentation)
(Not many people check all six boxes)
(Five-out-of-six BADA wraps up)
(BABYZOO's presentation follows)
(I take back what I said about no one checking all six boxes.)
(Disappointed, happy)
From what I saw...
- I thought it was totally over. - Right.
The direction was so good.
That opening close-up...
The look in his eyes, the mood. It all had such a strong impact.
It's the only one that really focuses on the subject.
That works so well as an ending.
Right. It's so good.
If they shoot it just like that,
- you can relax a little. - Definitely.
It's like having the answer key.
Everything's all figured out now.
Is BABYZOO crying?
My eyes actually started tearing up.
It was such an overwhelming feeling.
I can't believe my moment finally came.
As the missions went on,
I kept wondering if I'd make it all the way to the finals,
and I started to worry.
I kept questioning whether I had what it takes as a director.
And there were so many times I really doubted myself.
I thought I might not even get to show what I can do in the finals.
So I... I made the finals?
I can't believe I'm in the finals.
The best part is making the finals.
Now I get to go straight there...
so I'll take more responsibility...
and put even more heart into it.
Jun Hui!
I'm disappointed, but I am happy for Jun Hui.
I genuinely think he's amazing.
Kasper is genuinely rooting for me.
I'm genuinely so happy that Jun Hui became the director.
BABYZOO, let's get it!
Right now, I think the most disappointed person is...
Back Koo Young.
Jun Hui pulled it off.
Oh, Last Stage. Darn it.
Jun Hui, please save me.
I've been given the power to save one person.
(The clear-eyed madman)
Does he want to go to Last Stage?
I think it's about time...
I get to tease him for once.
He would never save me.
This is the first time I've felt this disappointed.
I'd been on a winning streak,
so I felt really down this time.
I hope Jun Hui saves me. Please.
Now I need to do all I can to get saved.
(The sweet taste of power)
(Endless applause)
In the brand performance film, the four choreographers...
will each be assigned one part...
and serve as its movement director.
(Part Movement Directing)
I thought so.
In tight spaces, tubes and such.
BABYZOO...
will review the movement direction for each person's part...
then choose just one person to save.
I know Last Stage is a very scary place,
so Koo Young definitely has to go.
I hope BABYZOO sends him there.
Jun Hui is choosing someone to join him in the finals.
Please pick me.
There's one important condition.
In the part you direct,
you cannot take part as a dancer.
(Part Movement Directing: They must direct one another.)
We take turns directing each other?
They've come up with another interesting rule.
We're creating parts just for the directors,
so I thought I'd have to study up quite a bit.
I've already figured out what everyone here is like.
We have great dancers to work with.
When you have great dancers,
it makes a difference in the result.
Together with BABYZOO, our movement director,
we chose the director and dancer for each part.
We'll now reveal each part's movement director.
(Part 1: Music and storyboard reveal)
For this part, we've built a curved hallway.
The choreographer will be hidden, then suddenly come into view.
I think this part plays on the fun of having a curved hallway.
The director for Part 1 is...
I think I can do a good job with that curved hallway.
I think the focus will be on making the performer stand out.
It looks hard. It could be fun.
I was torn between the two.
What you can express on a curve...
seems limited to me.
Part One's director is INGYOO.
(Part 1 movement director: INGYOO)
The director dancing in Part 1 is...
I do want to direct BADA.
She's the best performer here.
The director taking part as a dancer is BADA.
(Part 1 dancer: BADA)
(Part 1 movement director: INGYOO)
Yes!
(Part 1 dancer: BADA, movement director: INGYOO)
The best performer!
"Wouldn't BADA want me to direct her?"
That moment has finally come.
Will INGYOO be able to use my skills to the fullest?
I'll do my best. I have an idea.
This part is in a narrow hallway.
The dancers go from a jumble to an orderly formation,
as we move between those at the back and those at the front.
That's the concept for this part.
From order to disorder.
That kind of feel would be so cool.
(Who should it be?)
Part Two's movement director is Back Koo Young.
(Part 2 movement director: Back Koo Young)
I am a little worried.
It's a really narrow hallway.
Until we get to the set,
we have to rehearse just imagining the space.
Will it work? Will it be okay?
(Oh, this isn't easy.)
The dancer for Part Two is...
I feel like INGYOO won't come well prepared,
and BADA is INGYOO's dancer.
Tae Woo seems perfect for it.
The director dancing in Part Two is Kasper.
Good. That's great!
Kim Tae Woo as the dancer?
His arms are fast. They're long, but fast.
You know Kasper's go-to move.
(Kasper's signature: fast moves with long arms)
I should come up with ways to make Kasper stand out.
Let's reveal the next part.
The choreography takes place inside a room,
and that space will keep repeating.
We show the same room over and over again,
but keep changing the choreography. I think that would be fun.
The camera moves sideways like this.
- People dance in each room. - Room, room, room.
I like this part.
The director for Showcase Three is BADA.
(Part 3 movement director: BADA)
The director dancing in Part Three is INGYOO.
Yes! Very good.
INGYOO is...
so good at moving freely,
so I thought he'd be a good dancer.
BADA dances for INGYOO,
and INGYOO dances for BADA.
The exact matchup from the 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
When INGYOO dances,
he's fearless
With INGYOO's unique mood and vibe,
if I can just capture them on film,
I think I've got a good shot.
We'll reveal the next part.
When you start the choreography, it looks like it goes on forever.
Your movements and body lines...
all line up at once, like a fractal,
so this part should have quite a visual impact.
Did BABYZOO have me in mind?
I think he gave me a relatively easy part.
Even this move will keep repeating.
There's only one person left,
but the director for Showcase Four is Kasper.
(Part 4 movement director: Kasper)
Koo Young would be ideal as the dancer...
That's what we discussed.
I'm fine with whoever it is.
Koo Young has long arms for his height.
He really extends his arms.
(Part movement directors and dancers paired up)
They're judging scene direction, not the dancing, right?
The best director gets saved?
Yes.
You have to work like crazy. Got it?
(That goes for you too.)
- INGYOO will get saved. - Why?
Because BADA is his dancer?
(Last Stage: 24H)
(Last Stage: 24H, a final battle to avoid elimination)
(Available exclusively on TVING)
(Movement Cross Directing rehearsals begin.)
Thank you.
My part involved...
INGYOO doing movements inside a small room.
Since other dancers were involved,
even with the others dancing hard,
I had to keep the focus on INGYOO.
In a way, I had a tough part to direct.
I taped out the space on the floor to get a feel for it.
I wondered how she'd direct me.
I hoped she'd direct me in a way that brought out my best.
That's what I was thinking.
INGYOO, shouldn't you do this here?
What?
(That's the spirit!)
We can't leave that out.
INGYOO wanted to find his own soul.
I wanted his movements to convey that soul,
so I studied INGYOO a lot.
I scrolled through his entire Instagram feed...
to see what kinds of moves he likes.
I wanted to capture INGYOO's signature attitude,
so I decided to fill this part with different sides of his style.
Movements with INGYOO's own vibe.
About 6 or 7?
To improve the quality,
I tried creating a lot of movements.
Here comes INGYOO!
(With the group choreography ready, dancer INGYOO arrives.)
Seven, go!
(BADA's part rehearsal begins with INGYOO.)
(An intense gaze)
Just like a real villain.
(The villain appears.)
That looks cool.
Honestly, I wasn't sure.
I felt BADA had eliminated as many variables as possible.
Simple moves...
that were easy to synchronize.
It wasn't fun to watch.
Looking at just the movements,
I felt something was missing.
This is movement directing.
You have to radiate energy.
- Am I doing this? - Yes.
I'll show them how it's done.
This is movement directing.
I can't bring out her best in a predictable way.
My part doesn't have any special effects,
or a lot of dancers.
She has to do something all alone in a hallway,
so energy is key.
(An energetic forward roll?)
It'll look like this. Like this.
Then...
you'll turn like this as you roll.
A breakfall and a forward roll?
Out of nowhere in this part?
(Straight into a roll)
Dynamic action.
Powerful and energetic like that.
There are three eyeholes,
so I wanted to show three different versions of BADA.
One BADA focusing on sharp accents,
one with long reaches and big, sweeping movements,
and one focusing on facial expressions.
BADA is such a strong dancer,
and she's shown that so many times.
I thought, no dancing. None at all.
Why not show another side of her besides dancing?
(BADA is made to roll throughout rehearsal.)
That's it. Yes!
Nice! That was good.
This is how he's going to use me?
I wondered why.
What I really love...
is using my hair when I dance.
I love being in control of even my hair,
but after I roll,
my hair naturally falls in front of my face.
Nice!
But INGYOO doesn't know that.
He hadn't really studied me.
As long as the roll looks clean,
there's no risk in this part.
I felt like the roll was the only thing he'd planned.
For INGYOO,
I'd prepared 7 or 8 different movements.
But he'd only prepared one.
Honestly, even for the freestyle,
I thought he'd choreograph it.
The freestyle is separate,
and I'd like another one on its own.
But he left it entirely up to me.
A director has to trust the dancer.
(Part Movement Cross Directing: Back Koo Young & Kasper)
Arrived earlier.
Tae Woo, how's your prep for Last Stage going?
I'm definitely not going.
The situation got interesting.
We've never had this before, right?
Directing each other like this?
But what if the dancer gets all the moves wrong on set?
But we're not being judged on our dancing anyway.
- That's true. - You're right.
That'll add some tension.
I felt I had to keep him in check.
As it happens, in Koo Young's part,
I'm the dancer,
and in the part I direct,
Koo Young has to be the dancer.
I had a lot to think about.
My part is the fourth and final one,
with movements that form an endless loop.
I felt it needed a dreamy quality.
For this particular part,
I think taller dancers would be a good fit.
I thought BADA would be good,
but INGYOO and Koo Young...
(Well...)
It had me a little worried.
It didn't feel like a good fit for the song.
(Kasper's movement directing rehearsal begins.)
Set and go.
Oh!
It was better than I expected.
He's fluid yet powerful,
and his lines are beautiful.
I'm very satisfied.
I really didn't like it.
Among the moves he'd prepared,
some were pretty predictable.
For example, moves like this.
My arms and legs are short.
When I do simple moves like these,
I'm unlikely to look cool.
For someone built like me or INGYOO,
shouldn't you prepare different moves?
There are walls on both sides,
and it's really narrow.
It's narrow, sort of...
It's a scene like this.
Part two...
has a lot of dancers in a narrow hallway...
creating an energetic atmosphere.
The key is...
Kasper himself, really.
He breaks away from the dancers to create contrast,
drawing the focus to him.
It was a part that required speed and control.
As a dancer, Kim Tae Woo...
is nimble and quick.
Those fast moves.
His fingertips are strong, maybe because he boxes.
Grabbing and controlling things with his hands.
I should come up with ways to make Kasper stand out.
It was more fun than I expected.
Having such limited space...
actually made creating it more fun.
- Thank you! - Even at this stage,
I think it's turned out really well.
He was very satisfied.
I'm not sure.
It feels a little off.
It doesn't really match the music.
He wanted me to hang on...
and come down like this.
But I know...
it won't work.
They'll have temporary walls up,
not even real walls.
But he still wants to do it.
Fine.
I didn't have the guts to say,
"Bro, this doesn't work."
That was my little strategy.
Little by little,
I changed the moves behind Koo Young's back.
How I look on film matters, too.
It's about time for Koo Young to go.
The people want him at Last Stage.
It's Kasper's turn to go to Last Stage.
(Hyundai City Outlets, Dongdaemun)
(Time for a quick break!)
Amazing!
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War merch-filled pop-up)
- They turned out great. - So sleek!
- So many kinds of merch! - There are.
Such a wide variety.
Photo cards like these...
This is cute.
The key ring is so cute.
So cute.
Here's BABYZOO!
I like it.
- They made key rings, too. - They did.
BADA and BABYZOO.
- This pairing works so well. - This pairing.
This pairing is great.
Wait, what's this?
Like an ID photo,
you put your face in here.
If you want a Kasper key ring,
like I'm doing,
just make one and attach it.
It's like going back ten years.
Look at you.
(Kasper, the happy key ring guy)
Trading cards? What are these?
Let's pick one.
Try one each.
Let's see what you get.
One, two, three. Amazing!
(What surprised them?)
Amazing!
(BABYZOO and BADA both picked Koo Young.)
Next?
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
BABYZOO.
- Oh, amazing! - What?
What?
(This time, they're surprised to pick their own photo cards.)
- What? - What?
That's amazing.
(With the uncles looking on blankly)
I'm getting goosebumps. Seriously.
Let's all take a photo together.
Like this.
One, two, three.
(The directors enjoyed their break.)
Look straight ahead.
One, two, three.
(Standing stiffly at attention)
That's pretty.
It turned out well.
(INGYOO, come with us next time!)
(Fully recharged)
(NOL Festival, Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(A chance to see the TOP4 perform and take their dance classes)
(D-DAY of Brand Performance Film Mission)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Movement director BABYZOO arrives early to get ready.)
- Your first scene today is solo? - Yes.
Doesn't that put pressure on you?
No, I love it.
(Thrilled)
I love doing this solo.
(Bursts out laughing)
(Keeps breaking into laughter)
It was my first time modeling for such a big brand,
so I was really happy.
First off, I escaped Last Stage.
Honestly, that's the best part.
I'm looking forward to it.
(The movement director arrives on set.)
It's so spacious.
A huge cyclorama, even big enough for a mega crew.
(And being set up on one side...)
When I shoot demo videos for artists,
I often use my phone.
Compared to filming on a smartphone,
it feels a bit more vivid, I'd say.
More lifelike, too.
I think it'll capture the energy with more depth.
I'm really looking forward to it.
- Hello. - Hello.
Once we get the planned angle, we can shoot more...
- Freely. - In different styles.
Yes, great. We can capture it all.
All right.
When we shoot this part,
I think we should use the version with fewer counts.
Count, tick, tick, tick, tick, and one.
We need to play the version that starts on one.
That should let the dancers come in on one.
All right, let me check everyone.
How's the hair? Is it going well?
- Yes. - Yes.
As long as it's not too straight,
the curls should look better on camera.
A slightly matte look?
- Yes. - Yes.
Let's go for a take.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Let's do this!
It's a solo section,
and it leads into a flashback,
so I need to express my emotions...
in a way that comes across on camera.
(Amazing!)
I really wanted to do well.
(Headbanging with all his might)
Cut!
(The satisfying sound of "Cut!")
I don't think I've ever...
been the star of anything in my life.
That's a bit much.
I think it's good.
(Satisfied)
Thinking that this was mine,
I felt my body...
bursting with energy.
We should be in sync if we just match our feet.
Let's match our feet.
Since this commercial ends...
with the mega crew and my solo,
I wanted to show not just my dream,
but the dreams of many people.
The stage I've dreamed of,
how I'd feel standing there,
I wanted to express that through the mega crew dancers.
Free, yet structured...
that's how I wanted the iconic movements to look.
Let's match where we look, too.
We're not doing this.
- Yes. - Yes.
None of this.
This isn't a rehearsal.
Get into the right emotional state.
(Pleased)
I never once thought it was hard.
I was happy, had fun, and think I did a good job.
That was great.
Cut!
- I'm hungry. - I'm hungry.
But we're shooting soon,
so there's no time to eat.
I had this earlier,
and it's great as a quick snack.
What's that?
Well, it's...
It doesn't just contain protein,
but a mix of whole-food ingredients.
When you're busy like we are now,
it's a great way to get a good mix of nutrients.
Give it a shake.
(Let's give it a good shake!)
(Shaking away!)
(BABYZOO is so cute getting into the "Royalty" shake.)
Just do it like this.
Or the finger flick dance?
- What's that? - You're good.
- You're good. - Do you prepare this...
in advance or something? Teach me too.
(Smiling innocently)
Teach me too.
(Kim Kasper born in 1992 is amazed by his dance.)
Let's try it.
The shake melts easily...
in both water and milk.
It's easy to have it whenever.
It's very mild and savory.
It isn't too strong.
It's perfect as a meal replacement.
I really have a lot of protein shake.
It has grains, vegetables, fruits,
and plant protein in one pack,
so it's really good.
It'll be good to have it when you're filming.
It's simple and nice.
If you're all done,
shall we go back to filming?
- Sounds good. - My stomach is full.
Let's do this, everyone!
- Let's go! - Yes!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
We'll start filming.
Five, six, seven, go.
(BADA is rehearsing with the dancers.)
If I get immersed in it and dance coolly,
the video will look nice.
She prepared it ambitiously, so I should do my best.
I hoped she'd give a direction...
which could express myself as much as possible.
Good.
The part I'm in charge of doesn't have intense dance moves.
INGYOO's attitude.
His gestures and attitude.
It's the part which can show...
INGYOO's style the best.
With more power.
Seven, go!
INGYOO's presence...
and his energy which dominates the space.
- Yes. - Okay.
(Satisfied)
I tried to bring that out of him.
Keeping a straight face doesn't look as nice as I thought.
I think this kind of vibe would be nice.
INGYOO, why don't you look that way and frown?
Why don't you try making use of that string?
(BADA gives customized feedback to INGYOO.)
Nice.
(Explosive reactions)
She understands INGYOO very well.
She understands her dancer very well.
You look so cool. Do you want to have a look?
- Look. - You look like a villain.
You look cool!
INGYOO smiled proudly too.
She picked the parts which I could look cool.
Things I can do completely immersed.
(INGYOO suddenly starts singing Arirang.)
(Sseuri sseurirang)
INGYOO wanted to find the Korean spirit in the demo.
I'll help you find that spirit.
I included the movement...
of the Korean spirit which INGYOO wanted to express.
He's a villain here,
he acts all cocky here,
and he's cool here.
Then he expresses the Korean spirit.
It's INGYOO's self-introduction.
I wanted to make a part like that.
It was well-received on site too.
INGYOO, that's a great expression.
That was good. It's so powerful.
It's really cool.
The director gave such high praise.
I liked how he bumped into people.
It'll be very powerful if we took a closeup shot.
- Sounds good. - Good.
You know when the scene is so good...
that it makes the director want to shoot more?
And the director is doing exactly that.
That's game over.
He was getting more and more excited.
(Impressed)
INGYOO did a good job immersing himself in my direction.
She was thorough. I could see that she prepared well.
BADA understood me well.
She didn't try to cage me.
- We got cuts right away, - Cut.
and I could hear the director was satisfied.
"Did I do too well?"
Was I too into it?
I thought the outcome would be amazing.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You're the dancer now. - Yes.
Can Kim INGYOO...
make 100 percent use of me?
I'm thinking about how to direct Lee BADA.
I think I can make it fun.
BADA will do what she's good at.
Since she's a great dancer,
I'll draw it out of her.
(Part 1, Section Director INGYOO's turn to film)
(Starting to sing)
You should discuss with the director how you're going to go about it.
Okay.
- For this part... - The part I'm directing...
Dance-wise,
BADA showed how great she was.
I thought it'd be nice to show off other charms aside from dancing.
On a curved hallway,
she's pushed, bumped into a wall,
and she runs out hurriedly.
I thought about dynamic actions.
(Section Director, INGYOO, Dancer, BADA, filing starts)
(The first scene shows off her action skills.)
I love the start.
(Just the way he likes it)
Director.
If this is nice, we can change the direction.
After filming BADA running past like this,
what if that comes out?
BADA, let's change.
Based on what happens on the set,
INGYOO finds the answers.
For BADA, she thinks about the peak of the dancer...
in advance and comes up with everything before she comes.
BADA and I are similar in that way.
I can't do it like him because it makes me anxious.
Two, three, four. Yes!
- Cut. - INGYOO.
- Yes. - That's insane.
I loved it.
Let's move on to a forward roll.
Six, seven.
Seven.
(BADA rolls hard for the rehearsal.)
Nice. That's the vibe.
My worries are...
Will it go well with the previous scene?
INGYOO.
- INGYOO. - Yes?
The scene before this was very impactful.
But we passed by her for the last cut.
That's right.
The angle and the facial expressions are all great,
but I don't think it'll go well with the previous scene.
I'm in trouble.
(What to do?)
There was an unexpected variable on the set.
The forward roll didn't go well with the previous scene.
The next scene did not fit in...
with the flow.
Shall we come up with something coll?
- Yes. We just need one scene. - I just need to come up with one.
Rolling almost 100 times became meaningless.
It was a shame, really.
The previous scene was too good,
so I need to change the next scene.
It was a lot better than you thought.
Since I was directing BADA,
I prepared in advance.
But...
with the given situation, I ended up directing like my usual self.
I didn't intend it.
Actually, when you go scene by scene,
you need to calculate how it matches...
the previous scene.
It didn't seem like he was very well-prepared.
So many things have changed on the scene today.
After that part,
there needs to be a strong impact for people to get immersed in it.
How do I make that happen?
If you do something impromptu on a set like this,
that happens.
- A delay. - A delay.
All these crew members need to wait for the delay together.
INGYOO must've felt like he was under the gun.
The directing of this film itself was very spontaneous.
It felt very much like he was trying to clear up the mess.
Why don't you dance?
Like this.
Go.
(She pulls it off right away.)
Nice.
That's cool.
We can do that.
- Right? - You're lucky I'm your dancer.
I'm so lucky.
Lee BADA did a great job.
Isn't it practically BADA who made this?
Isn't this BADA's choreography?
INGYOO trusted me so much...
that he let go of me.
But when you just look at the end result,
INGYOO has made a very ambitious and impactful scene.
That's nice.
The ability to draw the best out of the dancer all the time.
The movement directing to suit...
the need.
- She and I were a good pair. - Nice.
- Did you see where I'd dance? - Yes.
- Where is it? - The place where we ran.
If it weren't for the show,
we wouldn't be doing this.
We wouldn't.
You directing me...
- and me directing you. - Right.
We did that, though. When we went to Lollapalooza.
(Right!)
- Tae Woo directed it, - Right.
and he asked me to join him.
We performed together.
Koo Young, get ready.
How did Kasper direct Koo Young?
Please put the blue screen behind him.
It's the only solo scene.
But with the editing later,
there will be multiple Koo Youngs behind him.
I'm really looking forward to it.
- Kasper. - Yes.
Which of the two dances will you do?
I have...
about six dances prepared.
I'm serious. There are about six.
I made many options...
just in case.
I wanted to make it so that Koo Young's dance suited the camera.
So I changed them bit by bit.
From here, jump and move to your left.
Like this.
In case this needs to go viral,
- I made the name of the dance. - Yes.
- The name of the dance. - Back when I used to speed skate.
- I miss those days dance. - Come on.
- Back when I used to figure skate. - Not figure skating.
- Back when I used to speed skate. - Speed skating.
- I miss those days dance. - You miss those days.
When Koo Young does it, you'll really see that he misses it.
What?
He misses it. Look.
He misses it.
Ready. The music.
(Filming using a fixed camera in front of the blue screen)
(Watching intensely)
Kasper made a custom-made suit.
It looks like Koo Young choreographed it.
Try to be more chill.
(Powerful movement)
You can be more relaxed.
(Softly)
Yes.
- I keep getting slower. Is it okay? - Yes.
The three parts in front are very intense.
Jun Hui runs,
and BADA comes out aggressively.
When INGYOO dances with the dancers,
the scene keeps changing with the transitions.
Only mine is about the mood, not the beat.
The dreamy vibe.
Koo Young's original dance style is very powerful,
but I directed him to dance more relaxed.
Reduce his serious vibe...
and add a bit of my texture.
I really like this reduced version.
And when you do the "miss it" part at the end,
lift your head...
so your proportion looks better.
That angle makes your jawline stand out nicely.
The last angle really brings out his jawline.
I really feel that.
He brings out the best in someone.
For both BAILEY and the kids mission.
His strength really lies in making custom suits.
He knows clearly what he's good at.
So he draws it out of you.
This is nice.
Okay, cut. That was the best.
The camera will move.
- We can find the right vibe. - Yes.
If you're filming with the phone,
I can hold it myself.
- The timing... - Yes, since I know the timing.
- Shall I hold it? - Please do.
The part I directed...
will be complete only with the editing later.
So I need to predict how it'd look like later.
I choreographed it, and I know at what timing...
Koo Young's afterimage would show,
so I filmed it once as a guide.
And the phone is light,
so I filmed it myself.
Kasper is moving the camera himself.
Cut. Nice. This is it.
(The filming continues as per the guide.)
When you edit a video,
you can choose if there are many alternatives.
But if there aren't, you can't choose.
I was being strategic.
If the director doesn't like it, I'll make sure he likes it.
- This doesn't look bad. - Okay.
Good.
He made sure the scenes could be used somehow.
"This is how you should direct."
He made it so both the directors and I were satisfied with it.
It was very impressive.
Koo Young, you're 25.
Then you're 18.
Each and every part you all direct is really good.
BABYZOO must be deep in thought.
Come and sit down quickly.
You have bad knees. Sit down.
(Section Director, Back Koo Young, Dancer, Kasper, Filming starts)
The key point to watch here...
The dancers will be dancing with him in that space,
so I had to choreograph it well in advance.
Despite that, I placed movements that make Tae Woo...
stand out.
Make a charismatic face.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Charismatic)
(Kasper rehearses with the dancers.)
It's so cool.
(Focused)
- It's so cool. - At the start,
you looked at the floor.
(Teacher, why do you keep looking at the floor?)
(A nightmare resurfacing?)
When you do this, it looks like you're looking down.
I'll open my eyes wider.
(Reflecting it immediately)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Eyes fixed)
- Should I look forward... - Yes.
- when I do this? - Yes.
Don't look down when you do this.
Why don't you look in front?
- I'll try. - Like this.
(When Back Koo Young inputs,)
(Kasper outputs it automatically.)
Tae Woo needs to stand out among the dancers.
So I tried to draw out strong faces and expressions.
- Okay. - Cut.
You look cool when you look in front.
Cut.
(The director is satisfied.)
The part which Director Back Koo Young...
is in charge of...
had no movement of the angle whatsoever.
I just gave him a narrow hallway.
Since it's a narrow hallway,
the dance needs to have a lot of layers,
and there must be an impact from it.
- Goodness. - He prepared it so well.
From the first take, I got the feeling...
that it was perfect.
(Meanwhile, BABYZOO observes the scene carefully.)
(Tilting his head)
- Koo Young. Can I ask a question? - Sure.
For this movement, are the dancers supposed to look down?
- No. - No, right?
When you do this, you cover your eyes like this.
Pose like this.
You come up at the end.
I can see you're getting ready for it.
You need to tense your eyes during that too.
Like this.
And make sure you move your hands in different directions.
(BABYZOO gives feedback to the dancers.)
Using dancers could make things worse.
- Yes. - Or really make it better.
It's one or the other.
- It could be pointless. - Yes.
Personally,
I place great importance on details.
I think it shows a lot more in a small space.
But the dancers' angles, timing, and texture...
could've been better.
When Koo Young was directing Kasper,
I helped the dancers with the details.
I wouldn't have come to the scene like this to begin with.
I'd have made sure everything was perfect and ready.
Moving on to the colored lights.
- Go up. - You need to go all the way up.
Feel the wall.
Don't rub on it.
He...
Let's try. Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, go!
- The end result was more polished. - This...
It's so charming.
He drew out the best...
in Kasper.
It was impressive.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
They're all neck and neck.
When I solely look at their on-site directing skills,
Kasper was really good too.
But scene-wise, what was impactful...
was BADA's scenes.
So I think we should check out the edited video first,
and if they're closely matched, we should consider the process...
and the flow of what comes before and after.
(Which 1 Section Director will be saved?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(4 judge seats placed in the Square)
BABYZOO will sit in the last chair. I'm envious.
Today will decide if I make it to the final or not.
I was very nervous.
I'm very confident.
I'm most confident out of the four.
I'm doing this to win.
I don't want to go to the Last Stage.
I don't want to go to the Last Stage until the end.
BABYZOO, please spare me.
Today, we'll decide who advances to the final round.
The result could change after watching the final product.
So I'm not sure yet.
Jun Hui must be feeling very pressured.
I know how it feels.
It feels very uncomfortable.
It would pressure him a lot, especially given his personality.
He'll have to choose with a very clear reason.
If I end up in the Last Stage again,
it means I'm as good as eliminated.
I look a bit ill, don't I?
The three people to go to the final Last Stage.
It can't be me.
I should be the director...
who goes straight to the final.
(The Section Directors are waiting nervously.)
(A message is sent to each Directors' Room.)
The moment has come.
Jun Hui, please.
Discuss well and choose who you want.
I'm fine, really.
(Fake laughing)
I need to guess...
from his back again.
Like a zoo.
(At that moment)
They're here.
(Judge, Kim Hyeong Seok)
(Please.)
(Seong Won Mo, Shim Jae Won)
The moment the judges entered,
I felt very nervous and anxious.
- Hello. - It's him.
- Hello. - Hello.
Jun Hui will choose who goes to the final.
Can you see me, Jun Hui?
(Jun Hui, I'm here.)
I need to be saved first.
I'll beg.
- Hello. - Thank you.
- I'll look forward to it. - Thank you.
I watched the on-site direction and the practice...
with the director.
When it comes to judging the process,
- I can judge well. - Nice.
- And I can tell you about it. - Nice.
- We'll need to hear it too. - Right.
When you watch it,
you'll see how some Section Directors...
drew out the dancers' ego.
You'll feel it as soon as you see it.
It hits you right away.
You could judge those things...
based on what you feel.
For me,
it all comes down to whether it's attractive...
or not.
I think that's the role of a director.
I'll focus on whether they're directing...
based on the storyboard.
I have the right...
to save one person.
(BABYZOO will decide 1 person to be saved.)
I need to judge very precisely.
So I got very nervous.
I hope Jun Hui will save me. Please.
Please, it has to be me.
I want to place first and go to the final safely.
I don't want to end up in the Last Stage.
I must survive no matter what.
Let's watch...
the complete film.
I'm looking forward to it.
(1 director to advance to the final will be revealed.)
This is more nervous.
(He agrees.)
(Brand Performance Film Mission)
(Synopsis: Some movements have not met their stages.)
(Each of them piles up their movements.)
(Part 1 visual concept: Framing in and out using curves)
(Part 2 visual concept: Compressed space, condensed energy)
- Koo Young. - Yes.
INGYOO.
I look good.
Nostalgic Kasper.
The protagonist.
(Knocking)
Yes.
For the five-person opening scene,
the movements are different from the typical group dance.
I mixed impromptu movements into it.
Yes.
I mixed contemporary style dancing.
It's cool. It looks amazing.
The moves are interconnected.
BABYZOO's hand acting.
Yes.
(Running fast)
It's so dynamic.
I run so well.
We're clearly fast. We look like runners.
(Extra filming equipment and software were used.)
My gosh.
Infinite space.
This can be done with a smartphone.
BADA Lee appears.
Part A, the hallway.
Rather than a choreography, they're dynamic movements.
Nice.
BADA is such a great dancer.
(Impressed)
That's an interesting camera angle.
(Nervous)
(She sure is cool.)
That's cool.
The key point of my part is Kasper himself.
He's agile and razor-sharp.
Kasper is basically the second lead.
Right.
Kasper feels like the perfect fit.
Bang! I love stuff like this.
Let's go, BABYZOO.
BABYZOO acts so well.
The part I took on is INGYOO inside the room.
I felt like...
INGYOO looked so cool.
I think I directed INGYOO pretty well.
If that buildup was intentional, it's very nice.
The first movement in my part...
and the expanding room go together so well.
(Totally immersed)
- My goodness. - What's with Koo Young?
This is so cool.
It's amazing.
I love the wings here.
BABYZOO's emotions look so great here.
A dimensional space.
The camera angles are amazing.
The edge of Koo Young's moves is incredible.
BABYZOO is doing a great job acting.
Here it comes.
BABYZOO in a tight, confined space.
He's running.
BABYZOO looks so cool. My gosh, what's that?
He's jumping that high?
Crossing over into a dimensional space.
BABYZOO looks so cool.
The ending climax part crafted by BABYZOO is great too.
BABYZOO is possessed out there.
(Amazed)
- My goodness. - The transition is nice.
The sense of action is great.
(Completely focused)
His facial expression is no joke.
Show us the finale, BABYZOO.
Even the facial expressions are spot-on, BABYZOO.
(ONE MOVES US ALL)
(You can watch their full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
Director, you went through a lot.
(Satisfied)
That was so cool.
I think Koo Young's part looks the coolest.
Was it because I was in it?
Thanks to BADA as a player,
an energetic part was formed,
which made me feel that I could probably advance to the finals.
Since I brought out a satisfying outcome,
I think I might be the one director...
saved to advance to the finals.
I was watching, completely mesmerized,
and only now does it hit me that this was shot on a smartphone.
That's right.
It turned out so well.
The quality is definitely good.
It's cool.
Since smartphones are compact,
the camera can squeeze into tight spaces.
The sense of speed and action plays a huge role.
I was so impressed right from the intro.
The section where BABYZOO choreographed...
- It's cool. - is great in itself,
and it delivered such a strong impact.
But since we have to pick just one person anyway,
shouldn't we examine this closely?
And I also want to listen closely to the process.
- Right. - Okay.
Before we select the one finalist,
a total of four parts are prepared,
and we are choosing one among them.
Personally, I liked Director INGYOO's section.
Looking at his directing ability on set,
I think it is a part where he pulled out a strong result.
Go down around there. Yes.
BADA is like a cheat code.
- Right. - Nobody can stop her.
I like that it has movements memorable to anyone.
A great player and a great director met,
and it feels like they drew out the character of BADA well.
I really liked it.
It doesn't look like there was a distinct idea behind it.
If you just told BADA to take care of it herself,
you'd get the exact same result.
Honestly, I think only I can pull it out to that level.
I try not to praise myself because it looks arrogant, but...
(As Director INGYOO demonstrates the movement,)
You just go like this.
(Dancer BADA shows off an even more powerful movement.)
Nice. We can do that.
I think it will work.
You lucked out with your player.
I'm really lucky.
If BADA were someone who normally did...
things like this and suddenly changed like that,
I'd go, "What? BADA has this side to her?"
But BADA always dances like that anyway.
Then how about the scene where BADA directed INGYOO?
Watching BADA's part, I figured my expectations were too high.
When I watched it live on set, INGYOO looked cool, though.
I wonder if it comes across a bit too flat.
It's a cut change that just glides past like this.
Shouldn't there have been more visual continuity?
I personally feel like...
the director might have gotten...
- the short end of the stick. - That makes sense.
Because she had to rely on limited angles in a confined space.
From the way I see it,
this is actually one of the most memorable scenes.
It goes room to room while keeping things simple,
and the building-up process...
was placed at just the right spots,
so I'd like to give that part high marks.
Let's move on to the next.
Director Koo Young's section.
Koo Young's section?
It didn't feel like Kasper's capabilities were brought out more,
which makes it a bit disappointing.
Regarding the movement, weaving the composition...
- into stepped formations... - It was fun.
was really interesting.
Sticking to the wall and pulling away.
- Right. - I was quite impressed.
I felt from start to finish that Director Back Koo Young...
was so seasoned.
When he first sent over the demo choreo,
- I gave him feedback. - Exactly.
And that was reflected 120 percent.
- Okay. - Cut.
(Okay, we got the shot.)
(Mic claps of high praise)
The visual I had pictured in my head translated very well.
- He has a lot of experience. - Right.
It doesn't feel like an all-out sprint,
but it's just complete.
But in Koo Young's case,
there were parts where BABYZOO intervened on set.
When I saw that, I thought it was risky.
Unlike the other sections,
my part involved quite a heavy amount of dancing.
So the more takes you do, the more exhausting it gets.
We had to shoot strictly within our physical limits.
Let us talk about the section where Director Kasper had...
- Back Koo Young as a player. - All right.
The moment I saw this part, I immediately thought this.
"Isn't this choreography made by Director Back Koo Young?"
It's probably because they know each other too well.
I feel that Kasper didn't make...
good use of the boundless space.
It felt like he didn't really get the concept.
The movement itself didn't feel so novel.
Or maybe a simpler layer?
I think it would've been better...
if that sense of infinity came through more clearly.
For the section I directed,
the director had an exact framework in mind.
So you could say my movement direction...
for what the director wanted was just flawless.
I bet the post-production on this must've been really tough.
It was hard.
But what was so cool was that...
how the dancer used his fingers right at the start.
On the storyboard,
I only gave the note that the hallway stretches,
with no other details.
Yet when he showed the movement on set, it was so cool.
The moment I saw that,
I thought it would be mind-blowing if the hallway stretched out there.
He gave you inspiration.
It feels like he's toying with the space,
since the hallway stretches out right after.
I really loved it.
Moves like that fit so well with that style of camera motion...
and post-production work.
- Exactly. - Those moves.
Actually, when I saw how proactively Kasper worked,
even shooting test camerawork on set, I thought he was...
the one who left the biggest impression.
Actually, this piece belongs...
to Director Kim Hyeong Seok,
and if we were simply picking great dancers,
BABYZOO and I should be the only ones judging them.
As the players.
- Right. - But we're selecting a director.
- Exactly. - We need a different perspective.
How smoothly they utilized their skill set...
to realize what Director Kim envisioned.
I think we need to evaluate all of that comprehensively.
Right.
(It's over!)
It looks like it's over.
(BABYZOO heads to the Directors' Room...)
(to select the 1 director advancing to the finals.)
What could BABYZOO be thinking?
I'm anxious.
Three out of four are going to the Last Stage.
Three-quarters are going.
I think the odds are 50-50.
The results are so neck-and-neck that it must be an agonizing choice.
I think they would evaluate multiple aspects equally.
I really don't know.
If they considered the behind-the-scenes process,
I feel like I'd shine even brighter.
Please.
Please save me.
If I make it to the finals,
I will destroy the stage. Please.
BABYZOO, please don't send me to the Last Stage.
This is hard.
The road to the finals is so long and brutal.
(Time for the final decision)
This is driving me crazy. Hang on. I need some time.
I'll just close my eyes for one minute.
I had to pick just one person to advance to the finals,
so it felt really burdensome,
and I wrestled with it so much mentally.
With these three judging criteria,
two of them were neck-and-neck to make the finals.
I'm writing down the rankings now.
For criteria 1 and 2, the 2 are tied.
But on criterion three, on-set directing and adaptability,
Director A edges ahead.
Director A gets 12 points, and Director B gets 10 points.
Even though the perfect score is 10, Director A received 12 points.
So Director A advances to the finals.
Your next directing mission is the Final Stage.
(Selection complete)
Am I heading over right now?
He's out.
Is he out to announce the results?
Wait. BABYZOO is holding something.
(BABYZOO)
No.
Where is he going?
(Looking away)
BABYZOO can't even meet my eyes.
(I'm going to the Last Stage?)
(Marching forward without locking eyes with anyone)
He's going over to Koo Young.
Is he coming to me?
No!
He's heading for Koo Young's room.
Is it Koo Young?
Come in.
Thank you so much for participating today.
- Here. - Good work today.
- I'll leave this right here. - Okay. Thanks.
(Bowing)
Out of nowhere, BABYZOO walked in carrying an envelope.
The result for the one finalist.
It seems like who gets to advance to the finals is in here.
I did get my hopes up a little.
Did Koo Young survive?
Only Koo Young survived?
He must be happy.
So I'm going to the Last Stage.
(Sighing)
Koo Young should go to the Last Stage.
He needs to get dropped into that inferno too.
(BABYZOO is back in the Director's Room.)
(Preparing the next envelope)
Wait, there are multiple envelopes.
(But only one person advances to the finals.)
It was a bomb letter!
That thing is like a "Death Note".
(A death letter bound for the Last Stage?)
(Chuckling)
What on earth is this?
What?
Is it starting up again?
He's coming again.
BABYZOO is coming.
He heads into Kasper's room.
No way. Is this the order of going to the Last Stage?
Okay. As long as it isn't me.
It's fine as long as it's not me.
What's the order behind handing out these letters?
Right as I was thinking that...
(Knocking)
You worked so hard today.
He bowed 90 degrees to me.
Thank you for your hard work.
That is a condolence bow.
Wasn't that polite 90-degree bow...
paying respects at a wake?
So this confirms it.
I'm going to the Last Stage.
I didn't make the cut.
This is a letter. Please open it...
when they give you...
the cue later.
What happens if I open it before then?
Then you get scolded.
- Thank you. - You know,
I'm getting ready for the Last Stage now.
I'm already ordering props.
(Avoiding his eyes)
Thank you for everything.
(BABYZOO leaves.)
I'm definitely going to the Last Stage.
I think he's only handing envelopes to the ones going to the Last Stage.
Look at BABYZOO's mood before handing out the final bomb letter.
Totally shaded in distress.
I really want to go home.
(Sighing)
(In agony)
(Groaning)
I hope this is the order of people going to the Last Stage.
Koo Young goes down first.
Kasper goes next.
And after that, it has to be INGYOO.
It has to be INGYOO.
It's me.
(BABYZOO)
He's going to BADA.
BADA, you did a great job.
- Thank you for your great work. - My pleasure.
- You went through a lot. - You did too.
This is a letter.
A letter?
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you for your hard work.
(He visits INGYOO's room.)
Good work, INGYOO.
Good work.
You hit your absolute peak today.
He goes to INGYOO with a smile.
Does that smile mean, "Goodbye, INGYOO"?
- I did? - You broke through the ceiling.
I'm glad to hear that.
This is a letter.
- Did you write it? - Yes, I did.
Isn't it a bomb?
A bomb... Good work, BABYZOO.
Good work, INGYOO.
(They all received the letters.)
(BADA)
The result is inside this envelope.
What could it be?
Shall we open the gift?
(Announcing the one Director advancing to the Finals)
(Surprised)
Can I open it?
It's finally announced?
What do I do?
(I'll hide for a moment.)
(Sighing)
(Without going to the Last Stage,)
(which director will head straight to the finals?)
(Announcing the one Director advancing to the Finals)
(Surprised)
(Sighing)
(Without going to the Last Stage,)
(which director will head straight to the finals?)
Director INGYOO, your next directing mission...
is Last Stage: 24H.
(Chuckling)
Last Stage does feel like...
my personal color, honestly.
(Accepting the result)
(Back Koo Young checks his result.)
(Reading carefully)
(Exclaiming)
"Your next directing mission is Last Stage: 24H."
Gosh, seriously...
I didn't see this coming.
The dancers' details weren't...
aligned on set during filming.
Do all the dancers bow their heads on this movement?
- No. - They shouldn't, right?
When you do this...
I stepped in to sort out the details with the dancers.
(BABYZOO sorted out the fine details that Back Koo Young missed.)
My eyes were already caught...
on the dancers' lack of detail,
which made it quite disappointing.
For INGYOO,
BADA performed so remarkably...
that his ratings are high.
But the actual shooting process was slightly less seamless...
compared to the other Part Movement Directors.
How do we bring that to life?
Like this.
(BADA was busy dealing with the impromptu directing.)
You lucked out with your player.
I'm really lucky.
(Only 2 directors remain.)
I might be the one director...
saved to advance to the finals.
I submitted the textbook answer...
that aligned perfectly with the evaluation criteria.
(Surprised)
(Your next directing mission is the Final Stage.)
(Kasper advances to the finals.)
(Director advancing to the Final Stage: Kasper)
(Muted celebration)
I can't believe this.
I have to take a photo of this.
It's finally happening.
I made it to the finals.
I'm so happy.
I won't have to go to the Last Stage again.
I'm going to the Last Stage.
(BADA's next directing mission: Last Stage: 24H)
(Your next directing mission is Last Stage: 24H.)
I'm quite shocked.
It feels like torture with false hope.
"There was someone who showed a slightly better performance."
Who is it?
If it were you, Director Kim,
which director's section would have taken first place?
What we are choosing...
- is a director, not a player. - Right.
A good director needs to communicate well,
persuade effectively,
and lead the flow smoothly.
It demands multiple qualities.
From that angle,
my choice narrows down...
to BADA and Kasper.
BADA is a full 100 out of 100 points.
She was perfect.
"She's the one."
That's how I felt.
Then Kasper suddenly showed up.
Taking part in directing so exceptionally.
When I watched him work,
it served as a huge inspiration on set.
Kasper is also a 100 out of 100,
but I think he smashed right through the ceiling.
That is pretty much how I felt.
I think you felt the exact same way I did.
Overall, that was my exact impression.
Thank you, Main Movement Director.
Congratulations.
Thanks to you, I have set foot...
- in the finals. - My pleasure.
Let us show them what we've got in the finals.
We're the new faces.
The two new faces.
Among the three choreographers heading to the Last Stage,
only one will be...
eliminated.
(Laughing hysterically)
The reason I joined this show...
Four years ago, I landed in the elimination battle...
and lost in the semifinals,
missing out on the finals.
That's why I came on this show.
I can't repeat...
the same mistake again.
Now that I'm going to the Last Stage,
my time has come.
You'll see the best piece ever.
I will pour everything out...
to become the director...
who snatches the ticket to the finals.
(Who will be the director to return from Last Stage: 24H...)
(and advance to the finals?)
(Brand Performance Film Mission)
(This film was shot on a smartphone.)
(Additional equipment and software were used.)
(Smirking creepily)
(Grinning)
(This is a weird feeling.)
(I'm just one step away from the finals.)
(It's going to be do or die.)
(I can't do this.)
(Sighing)
(Hugging)
(You can do this.)
(I keep having these close calls.)
(Is it driving you crazy?)
(I just want...)
(to let things go now.)
(We're going to be super strong after this.)
(I don't know. I just want to make sure...)
(I have no regrets with Last Stage.)
(We must crush it if we can. That's our only choice.)
(I feel bad for INGYOO and BADA.)
(I'm going to...)
(put on a performance that will guarantee my spot in the finals.)
(A sharp inhale)
(I need to make it look good.)
(The last object of Last Stage is...)
(It's...)
(color.)
(Last Stage: 24H)
(You've been given a unique color from the start of the competition.)
(You must showcase...)
(your unique directing style you built on your own...)
(and your designated color in one performance.)
(When I thought about the color, purple...)
(Back Koo Young's concept: Bruise)
(I wanted to convey the color...)
(with the techniques that matched my concept.)
(I can't have it any other way.)
(I must go to the finals.)
(BADA equals sky blue.)
(The secret weapon of my performance is me.)
(I'm a director who's only one step away from the finals.)
(I'm going to showcase all of my dancing styles on this stage.)
(So I'm going to survive this.)
(I wasn't too thrilled about green that seen.)
(With good energy and good art,)
(I'm going to paint my world green.)
(I'll stick to my style a little more.)
(This performance is the ultimate compilation...)
(of everything I do best.)
(I do think that I have a shot.)
(The very last episode of Last Stage: 24H...)
(begins now.)
(Nervous)
(I'm nervous to watch it.)
(Gosh, BADA is so cool.)
(She should do more of that.)
(It was close to perfection.)
(Back Koo Young is definitely making himself useful.)
(Are we in the finals already?)
(This is it!)
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(Amazing!)
(Where's the microphone?)
(I think INGYOO is going to sing.)
(For real?)
(He's holding a microphone.)
(I'll do everything I can on this last stage.)
(I have to sing.)
(His debut has been finalized.)
(I'll turn it into "Show Me the Money.")
(Really?)
(What? For real?)
(INGYOO made a big play.)
(I think you're just incredible. I mean it.)
(I cannot believe he only had 24 hours.)
(It sent chills down my spine.)
(This is anyone's game now.)